August Thorell

Frontend Developer



About Me

I'm a 25 year old Frondend Development student at Hyper Island with a great interest in coding. I love solving problems and have a interest in graphic design as well. Overall I'm an optimistic person who enjoys working with others and gladly embraces new challenges.

Skills

Coding

JavaScript (ES6, React, Gatsby, Node.js) HTML CSS PHP

Design

Figma Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator Blender

Contact Me



augustthorell.com



augustthorell@gmail.com



076 191 09 78



linkedin.com/in/augustthorell



github.com/augustthorell

Education

08/2020 - present Frontend Development Hyper Island

08/2019 – 01/2020 Media Design Södertörn University

08/2015 – 06/2018 Bachelor Degree in Cultural Anthropology Uppsala University

04/2017 – 09/2017 Sociology Siegen University

Experience

12/2020 - 01-2021 Femart Designed and developed a new website for Femart in Wordpress.

11/2018 – 08/2019 Sanoma utbildning I worked as a content manager where I produced digital study resources.

02/2018 – 03/2018 Berättarministeriet Internship during my bachelor education where I worked with storytelling for elementary students.

09/2014 – 06/2015 Östra Grundskolan I worked as form teacher with fourth graders in elementary school.